let me get this straight I park where
I'm not supposed to and that gives you
the right to punch my
[Music]
car
welcome to this not happening I'm the
host Ari shapir and tonight the topic is
melee ladies and gentlemen you know I'm
from The Amazing podcast we'll see you
in hell please give it up for my friend
yours Mr Jon
[Music]
Roa I don't care for the way people act
these days most of the time I don't like
the way people act uh I find everybody
to be very entitled nobody apologizes
anymore nobody says sorry sorry isn't an
apology anymore sorry has become a
sarcastic phrase it's completely
sarcastic now because everybody's
entitled you know sorry I'm a
sorry deal I'm a well you're a
actually you're a and a harvor
person uh but that's everybody's
attitude like
deal and it bothers me and I will admit
I am ethical to a fault because the way
I was raised now I was raised in an East
Coast Italian
Catholic household okay now I'm not
Italian because I'm adopted uh and I'm
not Catholic because I'm logical
but I was raised in that environment and
that environment makes you passionate to
a fault about your ethics okay this is
the kind of Italian Catholic house I
grew up in when I was 12 years old my
mother forced me to watch Good
Fellas she I didn't want to watch it she
made me watch it and and the there's a
scene in the movie where Henry Hill the
main character he gets busted for the
first time and he beats the rap in court
cuz he won't squeal and he leaves the
courtroom and goes out to the lobby and
dairo comes up to him and dairo goes you
learned the two greatest lessons in life
today never rat on your friends and
always always keep your mouth shut and
at that part in the movie my mom paused
the
movie and she turned to me and she goes
did you hear
that that's what it's all
about well he committed purgery actually
want to get down to what it's all about
uh crazy passionate household emotional
very emotional fights with zero filter
just unbridled rage in every argument
I've I've gotten so mad at my mom in the
middle of arguments where we're
screaming that I I would stop and I
would go oh what I wouldn't give just
one
time and my mom wouldn't even get
offended she wouldn't be like how dare
you you know my mom would go you and
what army that was her response to it
psychotic and it was a Catholic
household as I said too very Catholic um
how Catholic this is out Catholic uh
there was a framed crossstitch work of
art above the couch in the living room
uh and it was a poem a Catholic poem and
it said a little boy asked Jesus Jesus
how much do you love me and Jesus said
this much and stretched his arms out and
died that was above the
couch in the room where you're supposed
to have tea with
people we also had a statue uh when you
walk in the front door there was a
statue about this big there was a little
table and a statue on about that big and
it was a bust of bloody Christ from the
crucifixion that was the first thing you
saw when you walked into the house like
am I going to like this place oh there's
a dying Jesus with blood and snot all
over his face okay yeah I feel welcome
it was terrifying but my I swear to God
my best friend was Jewish so I would
chase him around the house with the
Statue all the time when he slept over
look what you did to me
Dan look what you did
je all right so that's the house that's
the house and that's how I was raised
okay so uh about three or four years ago
my mom got cancer now she's okay now
she's fine but she had to go through a
recovery period for a few months so I
moved home to try to help her through
the recovery period period and one of
the biggest rules about cancer recovery
is no stress you can't stress which is
going to be tough because this is a
woman that I've almost fistf fought
several times in my life so I'm just you
know we're cooped up in the house and
we're annoying the out of each
other but we're trying not to fight
we're just trying to keep it cool and
the tension's building and whatever then
finally one day my mom goes I feel good
today let's leave let's go out of the
house for the first time let's go out of
the house Sunday let's go to the
supermarket Market we'll make a big
Sunday gravy Italian tradition great we
go to the supermarket on a Sunday in the
suburbs which if you've ever done that
it's a nightmare okay it's
horrible there's cars everywhere there's
loose carts flying all over the place
there's kids it's terrible so
I'm already driving like oh
we're not going to get a parking spot
I'm getting aggravated but I'm like be
cool cuz you don't give your mom cancer
again just be cool right
now and there's a big douchy like SUV in
front of us and uh it suddenly just
stops doesn't pull over to the side it
just stops in the middle of the driving
lane and the car shuts off and the
driver gets out of the car and walks
into the
supermarket that's it doesn't put his
flashers on doesn't go like oh dude
I'm sorry I'll be right back nothing
just walk did you ever see somebody do
an thing like that and
they don't call attention to the fact
that they did an thing
it's like you just saw a magic trick
you're like what the just
happened did he just do that he did that
wait how did he do that did he do
that so I start honking I started
honking and I'm yelling even though the
windows are up I'm yelling I go yeah hey
you can't park here hey and my mom goes
stop it stop honking right now I go no I
won't stop it he shouldn't be parked he
do you see what he just did hey hey my
mom goes stop it you're embarrassing me
cuz now we're out of the house and
suddenly she has class all of a
sudden and my mom goes stop it stop it
and I go I will not stop it there are
rules mom am I the only one that gives a
about the rules and I literally
start doing the John Goodman speech from
the big
Labowski when he's in the bowling alley
with the
gun and when you do that speech to
people they don't go oh big Labowski
right they go what the is wrong
with
you so I we we have to pull around his
truck now into the oncoming traffic lane
and it's dangerous and whatever but we
maneuver around and we park and I'm very
angry and my me and my parents we get
out of the car my mom and dad say come
on let's go into the store and I pull a
super good fella's move right now I just
go you go
ahead you go ahead I'm going to wait
right
here because that happens in Good Fellas
there's a part in good fell is where
rota's girlfriend gets sexually
assaulted by the neighbor right and he
drives her home and then they see the
neighbor outside and she goes let's go
in the house Henry and she go he goes no
no no you you go ahead I'm going to wait
here and then he walks across the street
and beats the neighbor's face in with
his gun and I've wanted to do that so
bad in front of a girl for my entire
life could you
imagine do you have a boyfriend uh you
love him you like
him just imagine if he beat a man's face
in with a gun in front of you no you
wouldn't be making that face you
wouldn't be making this face you'd be
making this face you'd be the horniest
you've ever been in your
life it's
awesome
anyway so I go you go ahead go on the
I'm going to way right
here and they go in the supermarket and
I stand there and I just wait for the
guy and he comes strolling out of the
supermarket with a sixpack this
douchebag wasn't even going in to get
like medicine or some like that
like an emergency possibly enough
six-pack and he's smiling like he's
proud of what he did and he hops in his
car I race to his car I bang on the
window and he kind of jumps like w and
he rolls the window down he's like what
what's up and I go apologize right now
apologize say you're sorry and he goes
what and I go you had no right to park
here no right very dangerous say your
sorry right now and he didn't say sorry
obviously he didn't come close to an
apology uh what he did say was
you your breath smells and then he
drove
away and that hurts doesn't it your
breath smells that hurts real deep in
the soul doesn't it that's the worst you
smell insult there is there's no worse
you smell than your breath smells I
literally this is how much your breath
smells hurts I literally would rather be
receiving oral sex from a girl and the
girl stop and be like Joe you're dick
dick smells really bad and I'd be like
it does how's my breath your breath is
fine but your dick reeks it it's a
dick sweetie keep going we I'm
[Applause]
okay so uh he drives off and now this is
the part in the story where I think most
people would be like I've lost this
round time to retreat go inside buy some
sausage for dinner tonight whatever
uh but I decided that I was going to run
across the parking lot so I could
intercept his car before it left the
parking lot because I he needed to know
okay so I run across the parking lot
full speed uh he's coming he sees me
coming he's not stopping cuz he sees me
coming so now I'm approaching his car as
he's driving past me and he's passing me
not stopping I back like this and I
punch his car as hard as I can okay now
some of you are making a face like Joe
that's nuts you know what
you okay have you ever punched a car
when it's moving with all your might do
you know what it feels like
glorious that's what it feels
like it is the Hand of
Justice hammering down it felt
great until he stopped the car and he
opened the door and he just goes like
this he goes let me get this
straight let me get this straight I park
where I'm not supposed to and that gives
you the right to punch my car
and then he undid his seat Bel and he
stood up and as he stood he kept
screaming at me but I don't mean
screaming words at me he just literally
stood up like
this
and uh at that point I ran
[Music]
away I I didn't I never got that far in
a confrontation before I was like
that's that's not supposed to
happen and as I was running I could hear
him going he's going keep running you
and I did I was like I yeah well
absolutely I didn't need that tip I
know but I was so proud of myself I
really was I was proud of myself I was
like this is what my mom raised me to do
man you know she showed me good Fells
when I was
12 we had the
Jesus committing suicide thing above our
couch you sacrifice for what you believe
in that's what you do and I couldn't
wait to tell my mom what I did to defend
her honor and I went in and and I told
her the whole story story right in the
middle of the supermarket and she all
she said was she looked at me and she
just goes you make me
sick and I was like that's not what
you're uh that's not what you're
supposed to say right now that's not
what rota's girlfriend says and Good
Fellas he hands her a bloody gun and she
says she's turned on but I don't want
you to say that but I just you know
maybe a thank you she goes you make me
sick and we started arguing in the
supermarket like fullon the argument we
had been trying to avoid for 2 months
because she's trying to recover from
cancer here it is the is going down
and it's not only going down it's going
down in public and we are screaming and
at the peak of the argument I swear to
God the peak of the argument I just go
like this I just go I am no different
than
[Laughter]
Christ and my mom goes what are you
talking
about and I go Jesus saw money changers
in the temple he went into a rage he
flipped the tables that's like me
punching the car I'm just like
Christ and my mom goes you make me
sick and for three days for three days I
told the story to every single person I
knew and every time I told the story I
made the argument that I was not
crazy and for three days every single
person I knew said to me Joe you're
crazy and for three days I denied it
until I realized everybody I know and
love is telling me I'm crazy and I keep
saying I'm
not that's what crazy people
do so the point of the story is guys
Jesus was
crazy thank you so
[Applause]
much